If you answered Async Task, then you are correct.
To understand why we chose Async Task as the answer,
we can check the developer documentation. In this API
guide on processes and threads, we can scroll to the
Worker threads section. Right away, if you want to follow
along, the link is included below. Say, for example, that
you want to download an image from the network
at this URL and then you want to update the
UI so that it displays this bitmap. Well, creating
your own thread to download the image is a
valid option, but there's a lot of overhead to
handle in making you app actually thread safe. After
you download your image, you cannot directly update the
UI from a background thread. However, Android has several
options to run code that manipulates the UI to
run from other threads. In this example, yet another
runnable is created to get the bitmap result back onto
the main thread to update the image view. This solution
is a little cumbersome because you have to manage two
runnables here. To abstract away this complexity we can use
an async task and then to kick off the async
task. For example, when someone clicks a button, then you
just initialize the task, and then you can call execute
on it, and then pass in any parameters that are needed.
Notice that when you're extending the Async class, there's a
couple of generics that you need to specify. The first is
the type that will be passed into the do in
background method. So, if you want to pass in this image URL
that is specified string here and then in doing background
you'll get a string parameter. The second one is for the
type of object that you'll get when you get progress
updates as a task gets executed. We're not using that here,
so it's okay to specify that as void. And the third type is type of results
that we'll be sending back to the main thread through the onPostExecute method